Asaf Dulman

Frontend / Fullstack Developer



GitHub



052-8849813



asafdulman@gmail.com

Summary

Frontend / Full-Stack Web Developer with knowledge and experience writing single-page-applications. Experience with the latest WEB technologies such as React.js Node.js, Vue.js, and Angular.

My latest Project (React, Node, MongoDB) Animal Adoption Marketplace: Friendly

People oriented, B.A in Psychology, keeping the person in front of the screen in-mind when coding.

Tech skills:

- Programing in modern JavaScript (ES6) including Object-oriented programing.
- HTML5, CSS3 and SASS; PSD to a live page. Responsive design and & "Mobile First".
- MVC, frameworks, Single page apps and Flux state management with React, Vue.js, Angular.
- Server side, APIs and REST; Node.JS.
- Using MySQL and MongoDB for database.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2016 – Present Head of Publishers at ZipporMedia

- Account management of over 80 accounts, building long-term and trustful relationships with partners. In charge of all supply side video activity.
- Manager of Ad operations team. Creating daily processes and in charge of tasks prioritization.
- Experienced in data analysis, recognizing industry trends, and building strategies to reach both personal and team goals.
- Responsible for all financial reporting of the department.

2015 – 2016 TV Commercials Agency Producer at McCANN Tel Aviv.

- Managing full TV and digital media commercials productions. Responsible for the relationship with all company's high-profile clients, e.g. Tnuva, El Al, Bank Leumi, Osem and others.
- The position required intensive care with demanding schedules for around the clock projects, multitasking skills, close attention to details and excellent human relations.

2014 Freelance Sports online writer for israelsport.co.il

EDUCATION

2020 Fullstack Bootcamp at Coding Academy.

2014 B.A in Behavioral Science - Tel Aviv-Yaffo Academic College.

2014 Academic Diploma in Sportswriters and Broadcasters - Kibbutzim College.
2005 Maccabim-Reut MOR high school – Economics and Business Management.

MILITARY SERVICE

2005- 2008 Fully combat service in Battalion 94, Kfir Brigade – Senior Sargent

• Served as Commander for two years. One-year platoon senior combat Sergeant (010). In charge of the operation planning and executing complicated tasks in hostile terrain.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS & HOBBIES

- Sports Geek Deep knowledge and understanding of various sport fields, specialized in European football and world-wide basketball.
- Hebrew Native language, English Fluent